inrdeals.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - INRDeals | Where Every Deal is Worth!

* * *

At INRDeals.com, we respect the privacy of our users and understand the trust that you place in us. Ours is an SSL-certified secure site with an added security layer. In addition, we have a privacy policy in place that makes sure that the information you submit to this website is protected and the transactions are secured. By accessing and using our website, you inherently agree to the terms of the privacy policy given below. Kindly go through it well before submitting information to this website. Your Privacy is our Priority. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number, company name, VAT ID, physical address and whatever information is required to complete the action. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

When you register on our website or subscribe to our newsletter, you are asked to submit personal information like your name, email ID, password, phone number and address. This information is used to personalize your experience on our website and notify you of new services and offers that we bring for you. It also helps us secure your operations on our website. If you choose our affiliate services, you are required to submit your bank account details. All the credit/debit card details, transaction details and tracking information are secured through SSL. If you use the website as an anonymous user, we keep a record of your preferences and browsing history to give you a customized experience during the next visit. Your contact information will be used to notify and update you of INRDeals' online as well as offline products and services. You can opt out of receiving notifications at any point of time. Any personal detail is never shared with any third party for whatsoever purposes. We recommend that you read the privacy policy of any third party or websites mentioned at INRDeals before voluntary submitting your information to them. 

#### NON Personal Information

Your log-in details, browser type, Internet Service Provider, device's name, Operating System, area code, language and time zone are automatically collected and remembered for resolving any future conflicts, identifying and solving server issues and for improving our services. Keeping a track of our customer's behavior through his/her preferences, purchases and post comments also helps us in assessing our website's engagement and interesting segments. It helps us in developing the website to your taste and making it a fruitful and interesting experience, in turn. 

#### COOKIES

We use cookies, which are small data files stored on your browser to remember past actions, to retrieve certain information like previous actions and preferences. Cookies cannot read or update the data on your hard disk and pose no security threats. Make sure you allow cookies in your browser to enable us to provide you with personalized content and targeted services. 

#### UPDATES

Since our website is growing day-by-day and the internet keeps coming up with newer technologies, we might need to come up with updated security precautions and measures to provide you a constant secure user experience. Any changes to the privacy policy will be duly updated on this page.
